<idea-plugin>
    <id>com.ddlab.tornado.codepublisher</id>
    <name>DDLAB CodePublisher</name>
    <version>1.3.0</version>
    <vendor email="deba.java@gmail.com" url="https://about.me/debadattamishra">DDLAB INC</vendor>

    <description>
        <![CDATA[
          <b>CodePublisher</b> is a free and open source IntelliJ IDEA plugin which helps developer/s to 
          publish or share the complete Codebase or code snippet directly to <b>GitHub</b>, <b>GitLab</b> or <b>Bitbucket</b>.
          This plugin does not provide any git functionality, it only provides an easy way to keep the code in <b>GitHub</b>, <b>GitLab</b> or <b>Bitbucket</b> 
          for future references. 
          Many times, developers write good code for some POC and code goes into lost world after some time. 
          This plugin will help you to save and share your code in GitHub, GitLab or Bitbucket.
          
          <p></p>
          <p><b><u>Advantages of Code Publisher</b></u></p>
          <ul>
            <li>An convenient way to publish codebase in <b>GitHub</b>, <b>GitLab</b> or <b>Bitbucket</b> for future reference.</li>
            <li>Easy to create a code snippet and share with your friends.</li>
            <li>A non blocking way to share the source code or code snippet.</li>
            <li>Easy to work as it has been developed using pure java and it is free and open source.</li>
            <li>Does not provide GIT functionality but it uses some git functionality internally.</li>
          </ul>
          
          <p><b><u>How to use</b></u></p>
          <ul>
          	<li>Make right click on a project and select menu item <code>Publish project to GitHub, GitLab, Bitbucket</code></li>
          	<li>Make right click on a file and select menu item <code>Share code in GitHub, GitLab, Bitbucket</code></li>
          </ul>
          
          <p>License</p>
          <p>&nbsp;&copy;&nbsp;Copyright 2018 Debadatta Mishra(PIKU)</p>
          <p>Free and Open Source licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0.</p>
          <br>
        ]]>
    </description>
    
    <change-notes>
        <![CDATA[
            <p>1.3.0</p>
            <li>Initial version added for IntelliJ IDEA 2020.1.* </li>
            <li>Added support for other products like Pycharm, Webstorm etc</li>
        ]]>
    </change-notes>

    <idea-version since-build="173.0"/>

    <!-- Added support for all types of products like pycharm, rubymine -->
    <depends>com.intellij.modules.lang</depends>

    <extensions defaultExtensionNs="com.intellij">

    </extensions>

    <actions>
        <action id="codePubId" class="com.ddlab.tornado.actions.CodePublishAction">
            <add-to-group group-id="ProjectViewPopupMenu" anchor="first"/>
        </action>

        <action id="snippetId" class="com.ddlab.tornado.actions.SnippetCreateAction">
            <add-to-group group-id="ProjectViewPopupMenu" anchor="first"/>
            <add-to-group group-id="EditorPopupMenu" anchor="first"/>
        </action>

    </actions>

</idea-plugin>